
export const dataLevels = [

    {
        id:1,
        title: "Beginner lvl Qestion 1",
        question:'Which unit is more powerful?',
        answer: [`Archangel`, `Black Dragon`, `Titan`, `Azure Dragon`],
        correctAnswer: `Azure Dragon`,
        level: 'beginner',
    },

    {
        id:2,
        title: "Qestion 2",
        question: 'How many gold/day gives you  a capitol?',
        answer: [`3000`, `5000`, `4000`, `40000,`],
        correctAnswer: `4000`,
        level: 'beginner',

    },
    { id:3,
        title: "Qestion 3",
        question: 'Chose the name of heroe, who have default spell - lightning chain?',
        answer: [`Sandro`, `Solmir`, `Xeron`, `Jog,`],
        correctAnswer: `Solmir`,
        level: 'beginner',
    },
    {
        id:4,
        title: "Qestion 4",
        question: 'Which "Town" gives you ability to have a double-mana?',
        answer: [`Tower`, `Castle`, `Dungeon`, `Inferno,`],
        correctAnswer:`Dungeon`,
        level: 'beginner',
    },
    {
        id:5,
        title: "Qestion 5",
        question: 'How many items you need to combine a Statue of Legion?',
        answer: [`5`, `6`, `7`, `4,`],
        correctAnswer: `5`,
        level: 'beginner',
    },
    {
        id:6,
        title: "Qestion 6",
        question: 'Which artifacte gives you "explosion" spell into your spellbock?',
        answer: [`Wizard's Well,`, `Crown of Dragontooth,`, `Helm of Chaos,`, `Spellbinder's Hat`],
        correctAnswer: `Spellbinder's Hat`,
        level: 'beginner',
    },


    {
        id:7,
        title: "Middle lvl Qestion 1",
        question: 'Which unit have the best magic-resist?',
        answer: [`Gnome`, `Unicorn`, `Diamond-golem`, `Steel-golem`],
        correctAnswer: `Diamond-golem`,
        level: 'middle',
    },
    {
        id:8,
        title: "Qestion 2",
        question: 'Choose the name of heroe who start with tier-4 units"?',
        answer: [`Tan`,`Bron`, `Roland`, `Octavia`],
        correctAnswer:`Bron`,
        level: 'middle',

    },
    { id:9,
        title: "Qestion 3",
        question: 'Chose the artifact that gives you ability to defeat any unit using battle magic',
        answer: [`Titan's Cuirass`,`Sphere of Permanence`,`Orb of Inhibition`,`Orb of Vulnerability`],
        correctAnswer:`Orb of Vulnerability`,
        level: 'middle',
    },
    {
        id:10,
        title: "Qestion 4",
        question: 'Which "Town" gives you ability to  see all game-map ?',
        answer: [`Tower`, `Castle`, `Conflux`,`Cove`],
        correctAnswer:`Tower`,
        level: 'middle',
    },
    {
        id:11,
        title: "Qestion 5",
        question: 'Which tier-1 unit is the fastest one?',
        answer: [`Pixie`, `Centaur`, `Hobgoblin`,`Oceanid`],
        correctAnswer:`Oceanid`,
        level: 'middle',
    },
    {
        id:12,
        title: "Qestion 6",
        question: 'You want to resurect unit,to save him after battle,exept spell, you need for this:',
        answer: [`Advanced earth magic`,`Orb of Vulnerability`, `Expert earth magic`, `Tome of Earth`],
        correctAnswer:`Advanced earth magic`,
        level: 'middle',
    },

    {
        id:13,
        title: "Master lvl Qestion 1",
        question:'Choose correct lvl when heroe can reach skill "wisdom" first time?',
        answer: [`2`,`7`,`4`, `6`],
        correctAnswer:`6`,
        level: 'master',

    },

    {
        id:14,
        title: "Qestion 2",
        question: 'You have a heroe without spellbook, how it`s posible to have it with 0 gold?',
        answer: [`Exchange it with other hero`, `Combine some artefacts`, `This is imposible`, `Exchange it in the artifact market`],
        correctAnswer:`Combine some artefacts` ,
        level: 'master',

    },
    { id:15,
        title: "Qestion 3",
        question: 'In Heroes 3 universe Angels are:',
        answer: [`Gods creatures`, `Ex humans`, `Souls of light`, `Robots/machines`],
        correctAnswer: `Robots/machines`,
        level: 'master',
    },
    {
        id:16,
        title: "Qestion 4",
        question: 'What gives you spell "view of air" on expert lvl?',
        answer: [`You can see all landscape`,`You can fly`, `You can see opponents location`,`You can see all resources`],
        correctAnswer: `You can see opponents location`,
        level: 'master',
    },
    {
        id:17,
        title: "Qestion 5",
        question: 'The maximum of treasure in Temple of the sea?',
        answer: [`20000 gold`, `40000 gold `, `30000 gold + 3 relict artifacts`, `30000 gold + 2 relict artifacts`],
        correctAnswer: `30000 gold + 2 relict artifacts`,
        level: 'master',
    },
    {
        id:18,
        title: "Qestion 6",
        question: 'What unit have immune to Cavaliers jousting ability?',
        answer: [`Champion`, `Pikemen`, `Crusader`, `Nomad`],
        correctAnswer: `Pikemen`,
        level: 'master',
    },

    {
        id:19,
        title: "Hardcore lvl Qestion 1",
        question: 'Your heroe did some moves, can he dig a Holy Grail?',
        answer: [`No,its imposible`, `Only if he have angel-wings/ fly` , `Only if he lost 50 move-points`, `Yes,he can,by exchanging units`],
        correctAnswer: `Yes,he can,by exchanging units`,
        level: 'hardcore',
    },
    {
        id:20,
        title: "Qestion 2",
        question: 'How many move-points require teleport on expert level?',
        answer: [`200`, `300`, `250`, `350`],
        correctAnswer:`200`,
        level: 'hardcore',

    },
    { id:21,
        title: "Qestion 3",
        question: 'Who killed Lord Haart?',
        answer: [`Sandro`,`Katarina`,`Nikolas`,`Archebald `],
        correctAnswer: `Nikolas`,
        level: 'hardcore',
    },
    {
        id:22,
        title: "Qestion 4",
        question: 'Which unit deals half damage against undead?',
        answer: [`Satyr`, `Psychic elemental`, `Mummies`, `Leprechaun`],
        correctAnswer: `Psychic elemental`,
        level: 'hardcore',
    },
    {
        id:23,
        title: "Qestion 5",
        question: 'Minimum of phoenixs you need, to raise 2 phoenixes with their rebirth ability:',
        answer: [`5`, `6`, `8`, `4,`],
        correctAnswer: `8`,
        level: 'hardcore',
    },
    {
        id:24,
        title: "Qestion 6",
        question: 'Which  cloned unit dont have special abilities?',
        answer: [`Obsidian Gargoyle`, `Phoenix and Ghost dragon`, `Arch devil and Mighty Gorgon`, `Vampire lord and sultan efreet`],
        correctAnswer: `Vampire lord and sultan efreet`,
        level: 'hardcore',
    },

]









